<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Bori Stats</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Bori Stats</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Ian Flores Siaca</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/page/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/page/about/</guid>
      <description>About the Blog This is a blog for me to write my opinions, tips and workflows. It will contain some analyses but the majority of the content will be (it&amp;rsquo;s me) giving my opinion about different issues related to Data Science, Education and the Tech world.
About Ian Ian is a data scientist with experience working with government agencies, NGO&amp;rsquo;s and educational institutions in Puerto Rico, the United States and Canada.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teaching Online - Coronatime</title>
      <link>/2020/03/12/2020-03-12-teaching-covid19/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2020/03/12/2020-03-12-teaching-covid19/</guid>
      <description>It is March 12 2020, we are in the middle of a global pandemic of #Coronatime, also known as COVID-19. People have been asked to work from home and you specifically have been asked to teach your in-person lectures/workshops/learning-transfer-rituals online. Now you might be wondering why the light tone of this text? Well, I’m from Puerto Rico, and TwitterPR has been exploding with memes about the pandemic, so might as well share some of that catastrophic joy with everyone around the globe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>/page/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2015 02:13:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/page/contact/</guid>
      <description>Contact Aenean ipsum justo, semper eu nisl ut, pretium tincidunt sem. Praesent et diam sit amet lacus lobortis dictum a id lacus. Quisque hendrerit sit amet turpis eu varius. Ut id lorem ac felis ultrices tincidunt. Pellentesque consequat arcu ac fringilla imperdiet. Phasellus pellentesque, sapien non pulvinar blandit, sapien ante aliquet felis, vel porttitor sapien ante in lacus. Fusce non urna aliquet, malesuada nibh vel, luctus urna. Phasellus ut lacus molestie, varius purus quis, malesuada lorem.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My awesome project</title>
      <link>/project/my-awesome-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2014 02:13:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/my-awesome-project/</guid>
      <description>About project Aenean ipsum justo, semper eu nisl ut, pretium tincidunt sem. Praesent et diam sit amet lacus lobortis dictum a id lacus. Quisque hendrerit sit amet turpis eu varius. Ut id lorem ac felis ultrices tincidunt. Pellentesque consequat arcu ac fringilla imperdiet. Phasellus pellentesque, sapien non pulvinar blandit, sapien ante aliquet felis, vel porttitor sapien ante in lacus. Fusce non urna aliquet, malesuada nibh vel, luctus urna. Phasellus ut lacus molestie, varius purus quis, malesuada lorem.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>